<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>sighting on UFO History</title>
    <link>https://ufohistory.netlify.app/tags/sighting/</link>
    <description>Recent content in sighting on UFO History</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://ufohistory.netlify.app/tags/sighting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kenneth Arnold Sighting</title>
      <link>https://ufohistory.netlify.app/events/1947-kenneth-arnold/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ufohistory.netlify.app/events/1947-kenneth-arnold/</guid>
      <description>In his book The Report on UFOs, Edward Ruppelt provides the following account:
 Arnold had taken off from Chehalis, Washington, intending to fly to Yakima, Washington. About 3:00P.M. he arrived in the vicinity of Mount Rainier. There was a Marine Corps C-46 transport plane lost in the Mount Rainier area, so Arnold decided to fly around awhile and look for it. He was looking down at the ground when suddenly he noticed a series of bright flashes off to his left.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lake Mead Sighting</title>
      <link>https://ufohistory.netlify.app/events/1947-lake-mead/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ufohistory.netlify.app/events/1947-lake-mead/</guid>
      <description>In his book The Report on UFOs, Edward Ruppelt provides the following account:
 An Air Force pilot in an F-51 was flying near Lake Mead, Nevada, when he saw a formation of five or six circular objects off his right wing. This was about three-fifteen in the afternoon.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mantell Incident</title>
      <link>https://ufohistory.netlify.app/events/1948-mantell-incident/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ufohistory.netlify.app/events/1948-mantell-incident/</guid>
      <description>In his book The Report on UFOs, Edward Ruppelt provides the following account:
 On January 7 all of the late papers in the U.S. carried headlines similar to those in the Louisville Courier: &amp;ldquo;F-51 and Capt. Mantell Destroyed Chasing Flying Saucer.&amp;rdquo; This was Volume I of &amp;ldquo;The Classics,&amp;rdquo; the Mantell Incident.
At one-fifteen on that afternoon the control tower operators at Godman AFB, outside Louisville, Kentucky, received a telephone call from the Kentucky State Highway Patrol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maxwell AFB Sighting</title>
      <link>https://ufohistory.netlify.app/events/1947-maxwell-afb/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ufohistory.netlify.app/events/1947-maxwell-afb/</guid>
      <description>In his book The Report on UFOs, Edward Ruppelt provides the following account:
 That night at nine-twenty, four Air Force officers, two pilots, and two intelligence officers from Maxwell AFB in Montgomery, Alabama, saw a bright light traveling across the sky. It was first seen just above the horizon, and as it traveled toward the observers it &amp;ldquo;zigzagged,&amp;rdquo; with bursts of high speed. When it was directly overhead it made a sharp 90-degree turn and was lost from view as it traveled south.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Muroc Air Base Sighting</title>
      <link>https://ufohistory.netlify.app/events/1947-muroc-air-base/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ufohistory.netlify.app/events/1947-muroc-air-base/</guid>
      <description>In his book The Report on UFOs, Edward Ruppelt provides the following account:
 According to the old hands at ATIC, the first sighting that really made the Air Force take a deep interest in UFO&amp;rsquo;s occurred on July 8 at Muroc Air Base (now Edwards AFB), the supersecret Air Force test center in the Mojave Desert of California. At 10:10A.M. a test pilot was running up the engine of the then new XP-84 in preparation for a test flight.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Portland, Oregon Sighting</title>
      <link>https://ufohistory.netlify.app/events/1947-portland-oregon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ufohistory.netlify.app/events/1947-portland-oregon/</guid>
      <description>In his book The Report on UFOs, Edward Ruppelt provides the following account:
 The week of July 4, 1947, set a record for reports that was not broken until 1952. The center of activity was the Portland, Oregon, area. At 11:00A.M. a carload of people driving near Redmond saw four disk-shaped objects streaking past Mount Jefferson. At 1:05P.M. a policeman was in the parking lot behind the Portland City Police Headquarters when he noticed some pigeons suddenly began to flutter around as if they were scared.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>United Airlines Sighting (Emmett, Idaho)</title>
      <link>https://ufohistory.netlify.app/events/1947-emmett-idaho/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ufohistory.netlify.app/events/1947-emmett-idaho/</guid>
      <description>In his book The Report on UFOs, Edward Ruppelt provides the following account:
 That night [4th July 1947] a United Airlines crew flying near Emmett, Idaho, saw five. The pilot&amp;rsquo;s report read:
 Five &amp;ldquo;somethings,&amp;rdquo; which were thin and smooth on the bottom and rough-appearing on top, were seen silhouetted against the sunset shortly after the plane took off from Boise at 8:04P.M. We saw them clearly. We followed them in a northeasterly direction for about 45 miles.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>